const wayfinder = {
  start: {
    question: 'Are you a grandparent?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'yes', goto: 'live-with' },
      { answer: 'no', goto: 'close-fam' }
    ]
  },
  'live-with': {
    question: 'Does a grandchild live with you?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'yes', goto: 'kc-rights' },
      { answer: 'no', goto: 'lost-contact' }
    ]
  },
  'kc-rights': {
    question:
      'Based on your answers, it looks like you might be a kinship carer. \n Do you need help understanding your rights as a kinship carer?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'yes', goto: 'need-advice' },
      { answer: 'no', goto: 'info-kc' }
    ]
  },
  'need-advice': {
    question:
      'If you need advice, our team can help. Please answer a few questions to help us understand your situation and get in touch with you.',
    options: [{ answer: 'continue', goto: 'legal-order' }]
  },
  'close-fam': {
    question:
      "Are you a close family member or friend who is looking after someone else's child?",
    options: [
      { answer: 'yes', goto: 'kc-rights' },
      { answer: 'no', goto: 'info-gen' }
    ]
  },
  'lost-contact': {
    question: 'Have you lost contact with your grandchild?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'yes', goto: 'info-lost-contact' },
      { answer: 'no', goto: 'info-gen' }
    ]
  },
  'info-gen': {
    result:
      'More information about <a href="https://www.grandparentsplus.org.uk/pages/faqs/category/advice-and-information# target="_blank">our services</a>',
    leaf: true
  },
  'info-lost-contact': {
    result:
      'More information about <a href="https://www.grandparentsplus.org.uk/what-you-can-do" target="_blank">lost or denied contact</a>',
    leaf: true
  },
  'info-kc': {
    result:
      'More information about being a <a href="https://www.grandparentsplus.org.uk/pages/faqs/category/new-kinship-carer" target="_blank">Kinship Carer here.</a>',
    leaf: true
  },
  'legal-order': {
    question: 'Do you already have a legal order?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'yes', goto: 'order-type' },
      { answer: 'no/not sure', goto: 'social-services' }
    ]
  },
  'order-type': {
    question: 'Do you know which type of legal order you have?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'yes', goto: 'select-type' },
      { answer: 'no/not sure', goto: 'complete-form' }
    ]
  },

  'select-type': {
    question: 'Please select the type of legal order below',
    options: [
      { answer: 'Special Guardianship Order (SGO)', goto: 'order-link-sgo' },
      { answer: 'Child Arrangement Order (CAO)', goto: 'order-link-cao' }
    ]
  },

  'order-link-sgo': {
    question:
      'More information about <a href="https://www.grandparentsplus.org.uk/local-authority-allowances" target="_blank">legal orders</a>.',
    options: [{ answer: 'continue', goto: 'complete-form-1' }]
  },
  'order-link-cao': {
    question:
      'More information about <a href="https://www.grandparentsplus.org.uk/local-authority-allowances" target="_blank">legal orders</a>.',
    options: [{ answer: 'continue', goto: 'complete-form-1' }]
  },

  'social-services': {
    question: 'Did Social Services ask you to provide care for the child?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'yes', goto: 'foster-carer' },
      { answer: 'no', goto: 'informal-arrangement' }
    ]
  },
  'foster-carer': {
    question: 'Are you a kinship foster carer?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'yes', goto: 'complete-form-2' },
      { answer: 'no/not sure', goto: 'complete-form-2' }
    ]
  },
  'informal-arrangement': {
    question: 'Did you make an informal arrangement to look after the child?',
    options: [
      { answer: 'yes', goto: 'arrangement-link' },
      { answer: 'no/not sure', goto: 'complete-form-3' }
    ]
  },
  'arrangement-link': {
    question:
      'More information about <a href="https://www.grandparentsplus.org.uk/informal-arrangements" target="_blank">informal arrangements</a>.',
    options: [{ answer: 'continue', goto: 'complete-form-4' }]
  },

  'complete-form': {
    result:
      'If you require further advice and support, please complete the form below and we will contact you within 3 working days.',
    leaf: true
  },
  'complete-form-1': {
    result:
      'If you require further advice and support, please complete the form below and we will contact you within 3 working days.',
    leaf: true
  },
  'complete-form-2': {
    result:
      'If you require further advice and support, please complete the form below and we will contact you within 3 working days.',
    leaf: true
  },
  'complete-form-3': {
    result:
      'If you require further advice and support, please complete the form below and we will contact you within 3 working days.',
    leaf: true
  },
  'complete-form-4': {
    result:
      'If you require further advice and support, please complete the form below and we will contact you within 3 working days.',
    leaf: true
  }
};

export default wayfinder;
